Explore the depths of our planet's oceans.  Experience the
stories that connect their world to ours.
Oceans is a documentary, family film directed by Jacques Perrin.
An ecological drama/documentary, filmed throughout the globe.
Part thriller, part meditation on the vanishing
wonders of the sub-aquatic world.
Self - Narrator (voice), played by Jacques Perrin.
Oceans (French: Océans, also stylized as Ωceans) is a 2009 French nature documentary film directed,
produced, co-written, and narrated by Jacques Perrin, with Jacques Cluzaud as co-director.
The film, produced in association with the Census of Marine Life, explores the marine species of Earth's five oceans and reflects on
the negative aspects of human activity on the environment, with Perrin (Pierce Brosnan in English) providing narration.
Budgeted at around $80 million, it was filmed in over 50
different places and took four years to film.
In North America, the film was produced by Disneynature and distributed by Walt Disney Studios Motion Pictures, who cut 20 minutes mostly
depicting violent massacres of sea animals (recreated through visual effects) in order to aim it at a younger audience.
The film explores themes of fish, sea, ocean, whale, great white shark.